Partnership for Rural Improvement Records 1968-1985
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Partnership for Rural Improvement Records
1968-1985
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
Archives 192
514 folders 17 linear feet 17 containers
Files include PRI programs, publications and task forces; research papers, annual reports, newsletters, etc. William Lassey's files include proposals to Kellogg Foundation, correspondence, PRI program developments, evaluation materials and relevant readings.
Organizational History:
The Partnership for Rural Improvement (PRI) was established in 1976 with support from the W. K. Kellogg Foundation. It was formed as a consortium of educational institutions, public service agencies and citizens to act as a catalyst for community improvement. Its objectives include 1)identifying rural planning development goals, and 2) providing a mechanism and a process for linking citizen-defined goals with institutional and agency capacities for assisting communities in reaching those goals.
PRI is headquartered at Washington State University. Since its establishment, the PRI has involved itself in such programs as assistance to pregnant and parent teens, task forces on rural crime, rural transportation, and railroad abandonment. Records cover the period from 1972 to 1986.
The records are arranged in six series. Series one contains PRI general files arranged chronogically excepting box 3, which is arranged alphabetically. Series two includes PRI's programs and task forces, arranged alphabetically. Series three is research papers and some of PRI's publications, arranged alphabetically. Annual reports, newsletters, fellowship and personnel and the some related reading materials comprise Series four, arranged alphabetically. Series five consists of statistics from the Pierce County Residence for the Future survey, conducted in 1974. Series six contains William Lassey's files, which include proposals to the Kellogg Foundation, correspondence largely referring to the establishment of the PRI, PRI program developments, staff meeting notes, PRI features and evaluation materials, and some relevant readings. (William Lassey was a professor of Rural Sociology at WSU.)
The Collection is open for research use.
Records of the Partnership for Rural Improvement Project were transferred to the Washington State University Libraries in 1984 (Accession Number UA84-32) and 1986 (UA86-14). These two accessions were combined to form the present record group -- Archives 192.
Washington State University. Partnership for Rural Improvement--Archives; W.K. Kellogg Foundation--Archives; Washington State University. Partnership for Rural Improvement--Records and correspondence
Rural development projects--Washington (State)--Research--Archival resources; Rural development--Washington (State)--Research--Archival resources
Lassey, William R., 1934- social science based rural development model: the partnership for rural improvement
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities; Public Works
- PRI General Files, 1
  - Kellogg-PRI, 1/76-4/76 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Campfield, 5/76-6/76 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - PRI General, 7/76-12/82 (Box 1, Folder 4-19)
  - PRI General, 1/83-6/86 (Box 2, Folder 20-31)
  - Budget materials, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Budget materials, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Budget materials, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Budget--purchase requests returned, 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Budget--central stores requisition, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Budget experiments of adolescent pregnancy group, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Memoranda and misc., 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence--Hagood, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence--PCAA, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence--Bill Gary, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hagood's file: re. Ed. 525, Foundations of Community Education, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Kellogg proposals, 1974, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Kellogg 1968, Kellogg-PRI, V,-O, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Communications re. Kellogg proposal, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Collaboration and integration in rural planning and development--a proposal to the Kellogg, 2-17-75 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Kellogg proposals, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - PRI-partnership rules and responsibilities (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - PRI general, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 49-51)
  - PRI general, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - PRI regional coorinating committee/WSU advisory group, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - PRI Evaluation short form ad long form results, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - PRI training/education, 1977, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - PRI documents, general, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - PRI proposal, goals, background, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - PRI general, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - PRI general, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Programs and Task Forces, 2
  - Reference information about computer (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Computer technology and local government task force, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Re. microcomputer technology and local government task force, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Economic diversity review group, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Governor's conference on rural development, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Housing review group, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Human service review group, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Land preservation, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - PCAA, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - PACC review groups, (cont'd), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - PCAA correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - PCAA facilitators, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - PCAA time survey (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - PCAA materials, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Public facilities, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Rural crime conference, Spokane, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Rural crime conference, Spokane, (cont'd) (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Re. rural crime conference, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Rural crime mailouts (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Small farms, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Adolescent pregnancy group-general file, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Basin issues-general, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Biographical material (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Career track-a community college program (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Case study of Kalispel (Indian tribe) (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Case studies, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Columia basin-newspaper clippings-U and I sugar beet growers (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Community education-working file, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 87-88)
  - PRI-Title V, community skill workshop, April 9-12, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Community skill workshop, Okanogan, April 22-24, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Community training consortium project-central region (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Curriculum outline for adult basic literacy and GED classes (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - External review of circuit rider planner program- Grant County, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - External review of the circuit rider planner role in the Grant-Lincoln-Adams county, 1981? (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Facilitators' workshop, June 1-2, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Fiscal management workshops, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Food processing industry information, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Game commission survey, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Group development sessions, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Industry and college project, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Needs assessment study group, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Needs assessment task force, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Needs assessment study group-final report, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Needs assessment, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Needs assessment-data draft report, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Plan of work, central region, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Plan of work, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Popular needs assessment, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Professional burn out-report (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Project development workshops-Higher Education (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Project team 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Project team--correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Project team approach to growth management (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Public forum, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Research, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Research, 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Sugar industry, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Communication workshop-farm women, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Summary tables-re. assessment findings and recommendations (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Review of research material-Big Bend subregion (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Staff seminar-shapes approach, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Workshop I (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Citizen participations in task force, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Impression of task force (Kate Sisson), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - RCC sub-committee on task force, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Regional task force on local government, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Rural trasportation task force mailing list (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Subregional task forces, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Subregional task force proposals, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Sustanability task force report, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Sustanability task force, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Task force-southeastern region, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Task force article and planning, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Task force-budget, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Task force chronicles, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Task force chronicles (revision), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Task force concept in rural development- notes, interim products, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Task force--eastern and central regions, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Task force/fellowship project, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Task force and fellowship announcement, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Task force-general, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Task force modifications for RCC meeting- Walla Walla, June 9-10, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Task force notes-Kate, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Task force on rural transportation, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Task force on rural transportation, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Task forces-Phase III, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Task force related materials, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Task force report, Okanogan, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 148-49)
  - Task force report, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Task force-telephone contacts, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Task force-western region, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Task force working paper, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Transportation task force-responses from staff members (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Transportation task force-meetings, March-May, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Transportation task force-meetings, June-Sept., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Transportation task force-correspon9nce, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Town of Warden, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Field staff notes (PRI)-central subregion, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Central subregion, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Grand Coulee By-laws (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Grand Coulee Survey-Ron Hunter Letter re. mailing permit, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Grand Coulee Dam Area-C. O. G. 1979 of Government?), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Coulee city newspaper clippings, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Grand Coulee, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Impact-Grand Coulee area, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Grand Coulee area consortium, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Grand Coulee area survey, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Grand Coulee windmill project, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Central subregion-community education, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Human resources directory (Grant/Adams/Lincoln), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Plan of work (central subregion), 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Central subregion area population (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Centralia College, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Central subregion, (PRI), 1980-1985 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Yakima, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Eastern subregion, 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 177-178)
  - Eastern Washington University, 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Subregional Committee Joint Meeting, Dec. 5-6, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 180)
    (cancelled)
  - Farm Home Administration (Fm H A), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Survey of business during the Omak Stampede of, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 182)
  - Southern subregion, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 183-84)
  - Western subregion, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 185-186)
  - Clark Community College (Box 7, Folder 187)
  - West Washington University, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Evergreen College, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - Western subregion, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - Almira town meetings, (fiscal management), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - AMAX, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Colville tribal police training program, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Creston, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Creston, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Creston-Mt. Tolman, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Creston, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Creston generating station conceptual mitigation program-version #3, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Davenport school group (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Electric City planning commission, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Electric City news clippings, fall, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Ferry County project (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Human resources office-region 9 (Grant-Lincoln- Adams), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - Grant County public transportation feasibilitystudy, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Transportation study report (Grant county), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Personnel-Bill Thompson (Grant county), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 206)
  - Grant county brochures (Box 8, Folder 207)
  - Evaluation request of the Conference of Fovernments- Circuit Rider Program, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Conference of Government-Circuit Rider Planner evaluation, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Transportation (Grant-Lincoln-Adams), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Community action survey project-Grant County, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Crab Creek Association (Lincoln County), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Murray-10th street, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Survey-Kiwanis Club of Moses Lake 1977-78- surveyed by Fred Huston (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Growth impact-extension project, Moses Lake, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 215)
  - Citizen participation, Moses Lake, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Northern Tier Pipeline Project (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Othello recreation district-first project, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Othello-history/information, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Othello-parks and recreation plan survey, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 220)
  - Ritzville emergency plan, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 221)
  - Possible foundation association for Ritzville Library project (Box 8, Folder 222)
  - Royal Slope, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 223)
  - Royal Slope-history/information, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 224)
  - Royal City, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 225)
  - Royal City Custom Cannery, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 226)
  - Walla Walla report (draft), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 227)
  - Walla Walla project, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 228)
  - Annual report to the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 229)
  - Annual report to the Interstate Commerce Commission-Burlington Northern, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 230)
  - Annual report to the Interstate Commerce Commission-Union Pacific, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 231)
  - A study of the transportation needs of people in southwestern Minnesota, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 232)
  - Analysis of railroad "Train Crew" labor costs in Oregon estimated potential savings (Box 9, Folder 233)
  - Citizen participation in planning (Box 9, Folder 234)
  - Freight commodity statistics-motor carriers of property, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Railroad task force (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Newspaper file on railroad abandonment and task force (Box 9, Folder 237)
  - News clippings (Box 9, Folder 238)
  - PRI railroad task force correspondence (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - Railroad abandonment-Burlington Northern (Box 9, Folder 240)
  - Railroad study (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Regional Coordinating Committee (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Survey returns (Box 9, Folder 251)
  - The White House Rural Development Initiatives, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 252)
  - Washington State rail plan (Box 9, Folder 253)
- Research Papers, 3
  - Staff papers, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 254-256)
  - An assessment of factors influencing commitment to the PRI at Walla Walla Community College (Box 10, Folder 257)
  - Case study reports, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 258)
  - External review of the Circuit Rider planner role- Grant-Lincoln-Adams county, Dec. 1979 (Box 10, Folder 259)
  - External review of the Circuit Rider planner role in Grant-Lincoln-Adams county, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - External review prepared by Olaf Larson, Patrick Madden and Ed. Moe, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - Interns and some guidelines, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - List of publications, 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 263)
  - Linking Knowledge and Action: PRI's Community Consultant-by Greg, Spenser, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 264)
  - Misc. papers by PRI staff, 1977- (Box 10, Folder 265)
  - Options for rural public service delivery, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - Proposal to develop a community service consortium in higher education, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 267)
  - PRI manuscripts and publications, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - Papers by Joseph Luther and Vick Ann Braglio, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Papers by William Lassey, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 270)
  - PRI bibliography (Box 10, Folder 271)
  - PRI papers, 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 272)
  - PRI papers, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 273)
  - PRI misc. papers, 1976-1985 (Box 10, Folder 274)
  - PRI; preliminary observations, analyses and literature review by James Anderson et. al, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 275)
  - PRI: Washington State University by Schwalbe and Hagood (Box 10, Folder 276)
  - The Price of Change: a growth impact assessment guide, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 277)
  - Priorities for rural improvement, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 278)
  - Program rational: basis for the PRI model, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 279)
  - Reflections by the partner-an oral history of PRI, 1976-1983 (Box 10, Folder 280)
  - Re. rural crime, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 281)
  - The Rural Development Strategy Project: Toward Involving Citizens in Developing Policies, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 282)
  - Small group facilitation workshops (Moses Lake)- a summary report, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 283)
  - Social impact assessment and railroad abandonment: three case studies in eastern Washington by Gordon Morris and Rovert McDaniel, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Re. values of community development, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 285)
  - Working paper series, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 286)
- Annual Reports/Newsletters, Fellowships/Personnel and Related Readings, 4
  - Annual reports, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - Annual reports (drafts), 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Annual reports, 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - PRI Forums, 1977-1984 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - PRI newsletter, fall, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - PRI newsletter, winter, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - PRI newsletter, spring 1981, vol. 5, No.3 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - PRI newsletter, summer, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - PRI newsletter, fall 1981, vol.6, No.1 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - PRI newsletter, summer 1982, vol.6, No.4 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - PRI newsletter, fall 1982, vol.7, No.1 (Box 11, Folder 298)
  - PRI newsletter, winter 1982, vol.6, No.2 (Box 11, Folder 299)
  - PRI newsletter, winter 1982-83, vol.7, No.2 (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - PRI fellowships-fellowship agreements, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 301)
  - PRI fellowships-application forms (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - PRI fellowships-Dillman, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - PRI fellowships-fellowship evaluation reports, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - PRI fellowships-Frederickson, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 305)
  - PRI fellowships-Kelly, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - PRI fellowships-Khisty, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - PRI fellowships-Jean MacGregor, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 308)
  - PRI fellowships-Noffsker (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - PRI fellowships-Kiane Norell, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 310)
  - PRI fellowships-Plater, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 311)
  - PRI fellowships-"Buck" Rogers, Gonzaga University, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 312)
  - PRI fellowships-Julie Shattuck, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 313)
  - PRI fellowships-Throckmorton, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 314)
  - PRI fellowships-James Wavada, Maurice Feryn, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 315)
  - PRI personnel-Justino Balderrame, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 316)
  - -Bob Elk Belgard, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 317)
  - -Margaret Coon, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 318)
  - -Katharine Elliott, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 319)
  - -Ron Engeland, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 320)
  - -Jacqueline Farrell, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 321)
  - -Rick Fernandez, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 322)
  - -David Granatstein, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 323)
  - -Bob Hansen, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 324)
  - -Anneliese Hunter, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 325)
  - -Stewart Jones, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 326)
  - -Alfred Lewis, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 327)
  - -Elece Lockridge, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 328)
  - -Nick Lovrich, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 329)
  - -Otto Marenin, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 330)
  - -Dixie McKinnon, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 331)
  - -Teresa Mize, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 332)
  - -Gordon Morris, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 333)
  - -Edward Nigbor, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 334)
  - -Michael Notaro, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 335)
  - -Dwight Pace (Box 11, Folder 336)
  - -Joe Rogers, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 337)
  - -Mike Schwalbe, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 338)
  - -Dan Schwanz, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 339)
  - -Greg Spencer, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 340)
  - -Kate Sisson, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 341)
  - -Bill Tompson (Box 11, Folder 342)
  - -Judy Trefz and James Wittebols, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 343)
  - -Judy Wilkes and Abby Bryne, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 344)
  - -Dave Youmans, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 345)
  - Adult leadership-continuing education and training of urban planning (Box 12, Folder 346)
  - Copies of articles (Box 12, Folder 347-48)
  - Education considerations-Kansas State Univ., 1977 (Box 12, Folder 349)
  - The Field Program Associate in the PRI (Box 12, Folder 350)
  - The Guelph Development Outreach Project (Box 12, Folder 351)
  - Human service in the rural enviornment-Univ. of Tennessee (Box 12, Folder 352)
  - Indo-Chinese refugee resettlement in the US-- Univ. of California, Davis (Box 12, Folder 353)
  - Kellogg Foundation Profile (Box 12, Folder 354)
  - "Learning Never Ends" (Box 12, Folder 355)
  - Rural development literature, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 356)
  - Rural futures development strategy (Box 12, Folder 357)
  - System analysis for rural community services-- US Dept. of Health (Box 12, Folder 358)
  - Rural development perspectives, (USDA), 1981, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 359)
  - Small business development center: final report (WSU) (Box 12, Folder 360)
  - Reflections on community development education-- Austin, Bennett (Box 12, Folder 361)
  - Social Functions of Education, ed. by William O. Stanley et al. (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - Toward a Platform of Rural America, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 363)
  - Rural Community and Regional Development-- Univ. of Illinois (Box 12, Folder 364)
  - Re. Washington State (Box 12, Folder 365)
  - Public Affairs Leadership Program--Penn. State Univ. (Box 12, Folder 366)
- Statistics from the Survey of Pierce County Residence for Future, 5
  - Survey of Pierce County residence for future, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 367-372)
  - Survey of Pierce County residence for future, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 373-376)
- Lassey's Files, 6